No living creature was hurt during
the production of this show.
2 DAYS LATER
Bala Hatun, where do we put
the dowry of bride?
Put it in the tent our Bey and
Malhun Hatun will stay, Baysungur.
My Osman, you told me that
everything was fine.
Does it mean Umur Bey and his
tribe won't leave?
They're not leaving, my Bala.
- Then, to merge two tribes...
- To merge two tribes...
Umur Bey wanted a marriage.
What was your reply?
We'll have a wedding, my Bala.
Let the preparations begin.
Take care of bride's caravan, Gonca.
Don't worry, my Bala.
Salam Aleikum, my Sheik.
Alaikum Salam.
Osman Bey, who cares for his people...
who was given his role by Lord.
Welcome.
You are flattering me, my Sheik.
No, no.
You decided on the marriage...
at the cost of upsetting your love.
This decision could be made only by
a Bey who really cares for the future.
And also, only a Hatun who values her Bey
would consent to this decision.
We are proud of you both.
May my Lord bless you.
May Allah bless you, my Sheik.
Turkmen Beys are going to attend
in the wedding tomorrow.
May it be blessed.
Amin, my Sheik.
Osman Bey, may your family
become a beyship...
Your beyship become a state, your alps
become an army inshallah.
Inshallah.
Now, tell me.
What do you need now?
Our traditions must be laws, our castle's
be cities...
our people be victorious, my Sheik.
Everywhere we conquer shall be our land.
Also, our people...
must be satisfied by our govern.
You are right, Osman Bey.
What is your plan for Sogut?
I requested master builders from
the cities around.
They'll be working soon.
Mashallah (praise be).
While you are doing all of the works...
you should also care for
non-Muslims' rights.
As you know, sun shines the same
for everyone.
You need to be fair to everyone.
- Until...
- Until our traditions be like sun...
and shines all the people.
Kayıs' shall shine, our beyship shall
become a state.
I shall leave, my Sheik.
Bilecik Governor is back, my Bey.
Good, good. I want to see him.
- Send him my invitation.
- Eyvallah my Bey.
Did you send my invitation to
Sultan Mesud's man?
He is already on his way, my Bey.
Eyvallah. (thank you).
Have a nice day.
- Have a nice day.
- Osman Bey.
Oh, Mashallah (praise be)
- You show a great care in those.
- I picked them this morning, my Bey.
Goktug, buy all the fruits and vegetables
for the wedding from this Hatun.
Of course my Bey.
Have a nice one.
I'll join you.
Welcome, Osman Bey.
- These are not enough.
- All of them?
These would last months.
How many people will there be?
Haven't you seen a Turkish wedding?
It's also about whose wedding it is.
How can I know? I haven't
been in a Turkish wedding.
You can stay in the tent to help
Kayı Hatuns if you want to.
I'd love to.
Then, have a good day.
- Have a nice day.
- Eyvallah (thank you) my Bey.
- One more to visit.
- Eyvallah (okay) my Bey.
This is my mother's keepsake.
My tall mother's keepsake.
She had dark hair.
She passed her beauty to you.
I have been your confidant
since childhood.
Tell me why you are upset.
I am about to leave
my role and tent, Alaca.
I was my father's right arm.
The sharp sword of Kızılbeyogullari.
Now I am leaving all behind.
You are leaving for Osman Bey...
who you wanted.
I am going to someone who has someone
else in his heart other than me.
Why are you upset?
You are leaving.
So?
What am I going to do?
Why are we preparing all these, Alaca?
Because a bride has to have a dowry.
And a Bey's daughter has to have a friend.
So you are taking me with you.
You come with me wherever I go.
Betrayal woke the dark souls up!
Dark swears are out!
All the soldiers will die until I find
who betrayed Togay!
No!
Was it you who worked with Yargucu?
It was not me, Togay.
I do not betray you.
I'll scratch your traitor eyes out.
You didn't obey me.
I'll let Yargucu eat your eyes.
I'll put your eyes out when you wake up.
Next.
Camuha.
They are all innocent.
I was Yargucu's spy.
I am the one who betrayed!
Nicola.
You haven't had a proper meal for days.
I was going to enjoy watching them
killing each other.
Umur and Osman was going to be
each other's enemies.
Togay was going to attack like a
hungry wolf
But what about now?
They'll unite and attack us!
Forget about Umur Bey,
he is useless now.
Togay...
We have to remind him who he really is.
There's no other way.
How?
He'll come here.
He'll come to me.
He'll come to me sooner or later
to spit venom.
He'll come!
He'll come to me.
He'll come here.
I told that I'd made a sheath for my sword
out of the traitor's scalp.
I'll scalp you, Cumo.
It's your right.
Why did you betray me.
I have always been loyal to you
in my entire life.
Is this why you betrayed me?
I was scared that you'd disobey Geyhatu
and Genghis Khan laws...
when you rejected Yargucu.
I did this because of my loyalty
Now kill me, release soldiers.
Togay is as free as the horses running
on Khan Tengri.
Togay is ready to die in the name of
Genghis Khan.
Yargucu is dead for Togay!
There's no gold, no taxes from now on!
There will only be Togay's dark swear!
Why don't you accept that disobeying
Yargucu means disobeying Geyhatu?
Some stupid Yargucu
cannot show me the way.
Genghis Khan shows me the way.
I take orders from him.
I don't take orders from anyone else.
Forgive me, Togay, forgive.
Either you stand with Togay
for the sake of Genghis Khan laws...
or you die.
I'll obey Genghis Khan laws and the
protector of all Togay until I die.
I did everything for you, Togay.
You sad war was coming.
You overcame the enemy by letting them
think that you obeyed Mongols.
You set them against each other.
Now you are ready to trample
them both...
under your horses.
With the help of Allah.
Turks are parted in this land.
We scattered like sheep without shepherd.
Conquest is oblivion.
Our people are parted.
Karamanoglu wants Konya.
Germinyanoglu wants Enguru.
Hamidoglu wants Germiyan.
All are Turkish lands.
All are Turk.
You are fighting against the infidel.
None Turkish Bey can bother you.
Sultan told me Karamanogullari wanted
Konya.
However, as you said, what business could
Turkmen Beys have...
in our land?
We are surrounded by Byzantine.
They don't have any, Osman Bey.
Be sure about yourself so that...
you can destroy the enemy.
Even if it was just me left alone,
as Ertugrul Ghazi Bey's Osman Bey...
I'll fight until the last breath of mine
for my Lord.
We know what happened in Konya.
Sultan Mesud knows what is going on.
Seljuqs are just a shadow now.
Our Sultan can see everything.
I can say that.
But this shadow is above all the
Turkish Beys.
That he supports you was an important
step for you to manage all the Beys.
To end the conflict between
me and Kızılbey's son Umur Bey...
I decided to marry Malhun Hatun.
I am also here to inform you about this.
We already know, Osman Bey.
For Turkmens, this is a
priceless merge.
This priceless dagger is our wedding gift.
It is a keepsake from our ancestor...
Iznik's conquer Suleiman Shah.
May my Lord help me conquer Iznik,
where the Byzantine took away from...
our glorious Sultan.
This dagger shall witness
it is in good hands.
Amin.
I'll work hard. We'll conquer Iznik
someday, inshallah.
Inshallah (if Allah permits)
Osman Bey.
A man is always ambitious.
To take revenge that my father Noyan
left unfinished...
For Genghis Khan's bequest...
I am going to die for my dark swear
with souls.
I'll die with my honor instead of
being a coward like...
Yargucu.
If there is anyone who is scared
to take this way...
they shall leave now!
I have no business with cowards!
The wrath of souls shall be with you.
Leave!
Camo, bid your farewell to these cowards...
who disobeyed Genghis Khan laws.
We are less in number.
You can convince them.
They are dead to me!
Don't worry, we'll have new soldiers.
My new soldier for the laws of
Genghis Khan...
will be Nico.
Nico will hear we disobeyed Yargucu.
Nicola won't stand with us then.
He doesn't want to face Ilhanlı.
Nicola won't hear about this.
Brother, you are responsible for
the security of tents in wedding.
Nicola is looking for a chance to attack.
This is apparent.
- As to Togay...
- That dog loves to raid weddings.
He shed blood in my child's wedding.
He killed my Abdurrahman.
That dog attacks only the women and
children returning from the wedding.
Wait, where are you coming from?
I am from Germiyan.
Are you a messenger?
I am here to fight for Osman Ghazi.
Eyvallah, welcome.
Thank you.
Everybody I encountered mentioned
Domanic
I was there.
It was a great battle.
Osman Bey's brother Savcı Bey
became martyr.
- May he meet heaven.
- Amin.
The bigger a victory is,
the bigger the pain is.
I am here to fight for Osman Bey
as well.
Eyvallah, Eyvallah (Thank you).
Let's ask Osman Bey if he wants
to accept you.
Take his weapon.
What is this for?
- It is a gift for Osman Bey.
- Take it too.
Follow me.
We can set off after the wedding, if
you allow.
We have to see other grasslands
other than Domanic, Osman Bey.
Our tent is getting bigger,
our herds are getting crowded.
We are going to take each land
near Sakarya River...
from Byzantines.
Sakarya river is going to vivify our
tents, our animals inshallah.
Inshallah (if Allah permits).
Can I come in my Bey?
Come.
My Bey, an Alp came from Germiyan.
He wants to see you.
Let him.
Come.
- Welcome.
- Thank you my Bey.
I am coming from Germiyan.
What is the reason for your arrival?
I am Karayeli Muslu Bey's son, but I
want to fight under your flag.
Our order may be heavy for you,
son of a Bey.
Our way ends in battlefield,
we have difficulties.
Turkmen attacks Turkmen
in Anatolia.
Turkmen's sword cuts another
Turkmen.
Who dies is Muslim, who kills is Muslim...
Moreover, the land that conquered
is Muslim too.
You are the real warrior, my Bey.
You are the one who
fights against infidels.
You are telling the truth.
But infidels are not like the enemies
you know.
I have more enemies than friends here.
The best thing for you to think it over,
and come again.
Allow me to die for the flag, reduce the
number of enemy, increase the number of...
our friends, my Bey.
- What is your name? Tell me.
- My name is Turanalp.
My Bey, I heard you'd have a wedding.
if you allow, I have a gift for you.
Bring it!
What do you say, master?
It seems like it is made by a master,
my Bey.
Who did this?
I made it myself for you, my Bey.
I even did the handiwork.
It is made out of Damascus steel.
Eyvallah.
- Goktug.
- My Bey.
He must be travel-sore.
Take care of him.
Of course my Bey.
Brother.
Keep an eye on this Turanalp.
Check Germiyans.
They may have sent a spy...
to observe us.
Don't worry Osman Bey.
- Excuse me Osman Bey.
- Eyvallah (sure).
Osman Bey, I liked that valiant.
Osman Bey, ghazis are gathering under
your flag.
Don't worry.
Inshallah Bamsı Bey.
Inshallah (if Allah permits).
So, Osman Bey, your alps are increasing.
My mad son will cover my absence.
Not at all, no way Bamsı Bey.
No one can fulfill your absence.
I appreciate it.
Eyvallah Osman Bey.
Eyvallah Bamsı Bey.
We'll no longer collect taxes.
It's time to collect heads.
You should have attacked by now.
What hold you back?
Togay freed his soul.
He is waiting for the right
time to attack.
Is that so?
I salute the great soldier who
freed his soul.
What do you want from me?
That you tricked Umur Bey...
made Umur Bey obey Osman Bey.
If you want your fellowship with
Geyhatu to continue...
you'll give me soldiers
when the time comes.
A tasty and bloody price.
What about the taxes you'll take
from my governors?
The gold covered with Turkish blood
and the herds of them will...
make Geyhatu happy enough.
As to you and the other Governors, your
taxes will be paid by Turkmens.
I see the dark souls are combining
our fates.
It is time for Osman to die.
You said you were looking for a chance.
Then...
The wedding shall be a funeral.
Oh, you don't know about it.
Osman is going to make Umur Bey's daughter
his Hatun.
Do you know why?
To kill both of us...
he's making allies.
But you made a right decision
in the right place right time.
Attacking wedding will end this game.
Osman will take precautions in the
wedding. We'll wait for a better chance.
Prepare your soldiers.
Await my word.
I'll find a better opportunity.
Then, we'll get what we want.
Bala.
You look tired.
I am but it was worth it, Osman Bey.
All the preparations are done.
Why are you doing it?
Leave it to someone else.
You are the khatun of this tribe.
We have an important wedding, Osman Bey.
Our bey is marrying.
Of course, the khatun takes care
of things.
I've been sitting idle anyway. I don't
go to jihad or fighting.
I wasn't missed.
Malhun Hatun fought well.
You weren't missed?
When candles extinguish and I see nothing,
when I don't see these pretty eyes...
I remember you.
In my dreams, in battle, in heaven...
I miss you everywhere.
I found everything I was looking for
in you.
Umur Bey's tribe.
So, it's time for farewell, Malhun.
Leader of the Ghazis, Malhun Hatun.
She became a bride and
she is leaving.
From now...
your bey is Osman Bey
And your place is next to him.
Show him the love and respect...
you have shown me.
Don't haste to take your
bey's heart.
Be patient.
May Allah grant you a son, soon.
When Osman Bey hugs the son
he has been waiting for...
his heart will be yours.
Give me your blessing, father.
You always had my blessing...
may Allah bless you too.
You have my blessing.
Alright, let him pass.
I apologize. It's necessary.
We have to take caution.
Why don't you look at my eyes?
Pass. I'll find you at the tribe.
You can pass.
Alps, the gate!
May Allah fill your tent with
noises of children.
May Allah grant them a state
to rule.
May Allah give your daughters
worthy children.
May your tent find joy.
May you find happiness, Osman Bey.
Bala.
I know your love for me.
Tonight and many nights
I will grin and bear it.
Know that I accept it because of
my love for you.
May Allah give you a happy marriage.
May Allah give you happiness.
The wedding processional is coming!
It's time for you to take your escrow
in Allah's presence.
Alright, my sheik.
Alright.
May you prosper, Malhun Hatun!
-Welcome!
-Thank you.
Come.
Let's perform the ceremony with the
witnessing of Bamsı and Davut Beys.
Of course, my sheik.
Come, my sheik.
Umur Bey.
Here are the heads of those who
betrayed you, Togay. All are dead.
No one is left to take any news
to Yargucu.
Make sheaths for my warriors
from their skins.
They'll remember Genghis Khan's laws
as they look at them.
Let me give you a better gift
than their bodies, Togay.
Osman will take his herds
to the uplands.
They'll migrate, to Domaniç.
Here is the opportunity
I was waiting for.
Domaniç...
While Osman...
is having joy at his wedding...
Domaniç will be the grave of the Kayı.
Malhun, daughter of Umur Bey,
do you accept...
Osman Bey, son of Ertuğrul Ghazi
as your husband...
for 1000 dram of gold and
200 sheep of dowry?
I do.
-Do you?
-I do.
Son of Ertuğrul Ghazi and
Halime Hatun, Osman...
do you accept Umur Bey's
daughter Malhun...
with the dowry you accepted to pay?
-I do.
-Do you?
Witnesses!
Have you witnessed it?
-We have.
May Allah bless your marriage.
Amin. Amin.
Amin.
My Allah...
we witnessed the marriage
of these two subjects of yours.
You witness it too.
-Amin.
My Allah, bless this marriage.
-Among these two...
let there be harmony...
love and peace.
-Amin.
Let there be no hatred, discord...
or seperation.
-Amin.
My Allah...
give them worthy children...
long lives and prosperity.
-Amin.
Amin.
-Al-fatehah!
Welcome!
Welcome, Ayşe Hatun!
-Ayşe...
-Gündüz!
It's been a long while, Ayşe.
Welcome.
I saw you now.
I can happily die now.
-Inshallah you saw my son too.
-Of course, I did.
I went to Germiyan lands.
He was at the madrasah.
He counts days to come to the tribe
and become an alp.
He will be, of course. He will be.
But firstly, he will finish his
education.
I should help the women.
Come on.
Welcome, Ayşe Hatun!
Welcome.
When he became 20...
his cause got blessed!
Upon all the tyrants...
he is like a hidden giant, Osman Bey!
The student of Sheik Edebali!
May the lands of the heathen
get cursed!
The pride of Ertuğrul Ghazi!
Osman Bey is a special valiant!
He subjugated many nations!
He is the bravest of all!
He strokes his claws at the tyrants...
like a black wolf, Osman Bey!
With strong horses of
gray hair...
with well-made weapons...
with bold alps...
he wrote a legend, Osman Bey!
While the oppressed were
crying...
his heart ripped from chest...
he ventured forth for them...
to be their shelter like
a great tent!
He subjugated many nations!
He is the bravest of all!
He strokes his claws at the tyrants...
like a black wolf, Osman Bey!
Mashallah!
As my sheik father says...
this is the test I must endure.
Our sultan didn't send me only to
celebrate your marriage.
He knows about Togay.
Your agreement must stand.
Our sultan shouldn't worry.
We'll keep acting like the
vassals of Ilkhaganete.
If our sultan is gathering an army from
Konya, it's the value he is giving you.
The honorable banner of the Kayı
awaits the soldiers of our sultan.
Now, Kızılbeyoğulları too...
will fight under the banner of Kayı.
Soon! Soon! The subjugation of
the Turks is coming to an end!
Both the Byzantine lord and
the Mongols will kneel!
May Allah let me see those days.
Amin! Amin!
May those days come soon, Bamsı Bey!
Isn't it enough that Muslims suffered?
Kumral Abdal, thank you.
May Allah give prosperity to you
and to your lineage, Osman Bey.
Thank you.
-Amin.
-You are so beautiful, Malhun Hatun.
-Thank you, pretty girl.
I wish we could see Lena too.
-Inshallah we'll meet soon.
-Inshallah.
Gonca Hatun, where is Bala Hatun?
At her tent.
-What did Osman Bey do?
-He had fought the heathens!
What did he do for Malhun Hatun?
He had helped the ones in need!
Did he break hearts?
Neither did he do that, nor did he speak
any ill words. He married Malhun Hatun!
-Then, may Allah make them happy!
-Amin!
May you be happy for a lifetime!
If you allow me.
May our tent find joy with our
sons and daughters.
May your happiness last forever,
Malhun Hatun.
My Allah, help me control the
fir in my heart.
Give Osman Bey a child.
Give him children that are worthy
to his state.
Amin.
Thanks Gündüz Bey. He did the
most of the job.
It's our job to take care of the
women and the children.
-I'm asking tent by tent.
-May Allah bless you.
The foodbank at Söğük shouldn't
hinder.
They shouldn't be left alone
because we'll be at the upland.
I took care of it personally. The poor
people won't realize our absence.
-The food will be distributed.
-Good. Mashallah.
Welcome, Malhun Hatun.
Welcome!
Power to your elbows, women!
Welcome to our tribe, Malhun Hatun.
-Good day, Bala Hatun.
-Thank you, Malhun Hatun.
Come.
Mashallah, everyone is working like
bees.
-The migration caravan is already ready.
-It's handled quickly when it's parted well.
We should help.
Maybe there are families who
hasn't finished preperations.
We can provide mounts and stuff.
Don't worry, Malhun Hatun. There are no
people in need at Kayı Tribe.
-Osman Bey!
-Where were you...
when Nikola was killing innocent people,
soaking your lands in blood, Lord Leo?
I was in Macedonia. these happenings
disturbed me deeply, Osman Bey.
I want you to know that I don't approve
what Nikola and the emperor did.
I couldn't attend the wedding.
But I want you to accept my gifts for
you and Malhun Hatun.
I know that you are from the house
of Laskaris.
Everyone knows the animosity between
you and the emperor.
Your visitation here, the gifts
you brought...
the hand of peace that you extend,
I'm afraid they might be your end.
If I was afraid of my end,
I wouldn't be here.
My only fear is that Nikola will
end us all, Osman Bey.
By the way, I want you to know that
I won't kneel to Nikola's oppression.
Nikola acts like he bows to Togay.
His real intention is to weaken you.
But what he doesn't know,
or what he doesn't want to know...
-What is it?
-If he let's the Mongols oppress you...
it will be our turn then. He is playing
with the devil to stop you.
Nikola is a man who lost his way.
Our way is the way of peace
of your father Ertuğrul Ghazi.
Otherwise, it will be the end of us all..
Then, let's strengthen our friendship,
Lord Leo.
I'm ready to hold the hand you
extend for friendship.
Then, it's time to move to
the upland, Lord Leo.
As it was in your father Ertuğrul Ghazi's
time...
I'm ready to hold the valuable things
escrow at my castle.
-What is that, Alaca?
-A Rum girl named Zoe.
She has no one. She came from Söğüt
to help the preperations.
-So? -We talked a bit.
She gave it to me while leaving.
She made it herself. She said that it
looked good on me. Then she left.
A girl all alone, huh?
She is very talented.
Look how pretty she made it.
Talented seems little of a word.
She cooked, took care of the baby...
turned and tidied everything.
She put more effort into my wedding
than you, it seems.
-Alaca?
-What's on your mind, Malhun Hatun?
If Osman Bey sees it fitting, I want
Zoe in my service.
Our watchman have located to see
anything that happens in Byzantine forts.
Our alps will follow the migration
caravan, step by step.
-And they'll keep you informed.
-Thank you, brother. Thank you.
Our tents are ready for the upland,
my bey. They left before sunrise.
When the caravan reaches there, the
tents will be set.
Davud Bey set his smithry
at the upland, Osman Bey.
Now, our alps won't have to...
come to the tribe for horseshoes
or broken weapons.
Leo, the lord of Bilecik...
accepted to hold our stuff
for us while we migrate.
Osman Bey, this is good.
It's good, but...
I don't know. When Nikola
was so crazy...
Leo was our friend during Ertuğrul Ghazi's
time, but...
In these lands,
friendship is like a mad wind...
that no one knows which way it will blow.
You are right, Osman Bey.
You are right.
We are nomads but we make the lands
ours, sooner or later.
If Lord Leo's intentions aren't pure...
he'll end up dead.
We'll see, Bamsı Bey.
Lord Leo wants...
to stay a friend to me as he was to my
father. We will see...
if he is a man of his word.
You brought the burning heat
of Karakurum deserts to my room, Togay.
I welcome your wrath.
You remind me of the sweet yeast breads
that my mother used to make me.
You are different at every moment.
You brought the silence of the desert too.
Geyhatu's hunting dog got a smell.
Is your prey big?
Kayı Tribe will migrate to
Domaniç Uplands.
The road to the upland...
will turn into a blood river.
-So, you got your opportunity?
A prey worthy of a hunting dog
such as you.
What do you want from me, Togay?
Give me your best soldiers,
your best archers.
No.
Is not an appropriate answer
for this offer.
They are all ready. When?
Tomorrow.
Welcome, my bey.
-Thank you. Thank you.
-Come.
You too.
Let's go.
With the name of Allah.
You said you liked it before.
I made it again.
You should eat too.
Allah bless your hands.
Thank you, Osman Bey.
So, tel me.
How was your first day.
Will you get used to here?
Our customs are the same, Osman Bey.
It won't take long.
Inshallah, the women of the tribe
will get used to me as well.
Inshallah. Inshallah, they will.
They will.
It looks like you want fresh air,
Osman Bey.
You are welcome here.
You shared my bread.
If you want to leave now,
I don't want to force you here.
What are you saying, Malhun Hatun?
Why would I be forced to stay here?
Even though this marriage was to
unite two tribes...
at the end, it is done.
Now, we are wife and husband.
That's what I'm saying. The interests
of the two tribes are satisfied.
This marriage isn't only built on the
interests of two tribes.
What is it then?
Kayı Tribe...
found what fits it.
My food is ready, face is smiling,
and tent is warm...
whenever you visit here.
Come whenever you want, Osman Bey.
Malhun Hatun.
Good night.
Bala.
Tell me. What keeps you out of your
tent at this hour?
It was warm inside. I needed
some air.
-If so...
-What about you?
Why aren't you in your tent?
What do you think?
Now, we'll have such days, Osman Bey.
In the same tribe, in such close
tents...
but seperated.
I'll be alone...
and you'll--
-Be with your dream.
When did I ever tell you a lie, Bala?
When?
When did I ever betray your love?
Mashallah, shepherd leader.
Now, the sounds of our animals and
our carts...
will take over the green uplands.
Godspeed.
Mashallah. Gencebey!
You'll protect our right wing. Saltuk,
you'll protect our left wing.
-We'll be your wings and fly like birds.
-Thank you, Saltuk. I know.
Aygül, my girl. How are our women?
Do they need anything?
Everything is ready, my bey.
We prepared everything.
The supplies are all loaded.
We also keep the water cold.
Good. Good. Mashallah to my child.
But...
are the women ready?
We don't know what might happen.
They are all armed, my bey.
They are masters now. Don't worry.
Now, we should be on our way.
Now, our destination is the uplands.
May Allah open our ways.
Amin.
My bey, I had some meal prepared
for you.
I have some halvah too.
Come on, my child.
I see what's Cerkutay getting at.
You'll leave me hungry again, huh?
Come on! Come on! Come on!
Mashallah. Mashallah, my dear ones.
Caravan leader, is your caravan ready?
May Hz.Hızır accompany us.
We are ready, Osman Bey.
Mashallah, mashallah.
Bala Hatun, I choose...
Aygül Hatun as the she-leader of
the caravan.
She-leader of the caravan, Aygül Hatun.
May your days as a maiden end.
May you find an appropriate husband.
Thank you, Bala Hatun.
Osman Bey, when I look at you,
I see Ertuğrul Bey.
Good old days. We set many caravans
on these roads.
We saw many springs together.
Bamsı Bey, you never let me feel the
absence of my father.
You were his blood brother and
his companion.
If we see this beautiful spring,
it's because of you and our martyrs.
Thank you. But...
our time has passed.
Death is coming after me to unite me
with Ertuğrul Bey.
But, Osman Bey, you are the
future of the Turks.
May the Turkish tribes unite under
your leadership.
Inshallah, Bamsı Bey.
Inshallah. Now...
may our herds grow in number.
May Hz.Hızır accompany you on the road.
Amin. Amin, Osman Bey.
Mashallah!
-Godspeed. May Allah guide you.
-Thank you.
Thank you, my dear ones.
Thank you.
Let's go now.
Let's go now. We are going
to the uplands.
We are going to the uplands!
My bey, if you allow me, I want
to go with them.
-Go and accompany Bamsı Bey.
-Thank you, my bey.
May Allah clear your way.
-Boran.
-Yes, my bey.
Ready my horse. I'll visit my sheik.
As you order, my bey.
Everyone writes their own destiny.
We'll write the fate of these lands
together.
You, in the name of Genghis Khan's laws,
and I, in the name of the empire.
For our alliance.
I only ally with death.
I'll water the uplands of Domaniç
for the honor of death.
There is a great army waiting for
you outside.
My soldiers and commanders will
be in your order.
I can't wait to decorate my walls with
the skulls you will bring.
For the dark oath...
for the soils that are watered
with the lust of death...
in Genghis Khan's path...
may death honor us all!
For Genghiz Khan!
May your saints lead you to victory!
To victory!
This is the end of Osman Bey.
The sleeping devil has awakened, Helen.
Now, it's time for Osman's death.
What about these perfumeries? Shouldn't
they be on the entrance?
Right. Good smells should greet
the people.
My sheik, what do you think? We should
talk to the ahi guild too.
I want everyone to approve the development
of this marketplace.
This is the right thing, Osman Bey. It's
the merchants and the people who'll use it.
-What's important is what they want.
-Of course. Of course.
Osman Bey, we need to move the butchers
to this side of the marketplace.
My sheik, this building looks fitting
for a pavilion.
It's fitting, Osman Bey.
The marketplace isn't just a trading
place. It should need everything...
gardens and bathhouses too.
-Of course, my sheik.
-Who owns this building?
-We'll find out right away, my bey.
You will know who owns what here...
Muslims and non-Muslims. Everything.
-Now find me the owner.
-As you order, my bey.
My sheik.
Come on, my dear ones.
Come on, my dear ones!
Come on, my valiants!
Mashallah! Come on!
Come on!
How is the migration going, Osman Bey?
-The first caravan departed to Domaniç.
-Mashallah.
-Inshallah, they'll arrive safely.
-Inshallah, my sheik. Inshallah.
And about that building.
I've no doubt that your decision
will be just.
The real development of Söğüt
will be with justice.
My bey, my sheik.
The owner of the building.
-Welcome.
-Thank you, my bey.
If you allow me, my sheik.
Come, sit.
Osman Bey, you are the ruler of Söğüt.
How can I sit next to you?
Not at all. Not at all.
Come, sit.
Now, I'm a buyer who wants
your building.
But let's keep our titles aside.
So that our trade can be fair.
You shouldn't be forced to make an
unwanted decision via fear.
I'm grateful, my Allah.
Now, I want your building.
What is it's worth?
Be at ease. Tell what it's worth.
It has no value. Because I don't
want to sell it.
If you don't want to sell it,
then...
there is nothing to say.
You can leave freely.
It's true that you are just, Osman Bey.
May God bless your beylig.
Amin.
This justice you show to Allah's subjects
with no discrimination...
may it pass to your children.
May your beylig turn into a state.
May Muslims and non-Muslims...
find peace and security under
this flag.
Inshallah, my sheik.
Inshallah.
Osman Bey isn't here, Togay.
Who is leading them?
Bamsı Bey.
My bey!
-What's wrong, Baysungur?
-My bey, Togay! He left Nikola's castle.
-What about Nikola?
-Togay is leading soldiers and warriors.
-Do you know where they'll go?
-We have, my bey. To Domaniç uplands.
What are you saying? Alps! Inform
the tribe.
-They'll raid our caravan! Come on!
-As you order, my bey!
Bamsı Bey! Bamsı Bey!
These prayer beads...
After Abdurrahman Ghazi died...
I used it a lot.
Now, it's time for revenge.
Osman will lose a second father.
I'm honored that I'll be the
last person to see you.
But Togay, you don't know that...
the last thing we see before dying
is an angel.
So, take your sword.
Take your sword, Togay.
Togay!
Togay! Togay! Get up!
Get up!
Warriors! Warriors!
Kill them!
Bamsı Bey!
Bamsı Bey! Bamsı Bey!
-Bamsı Bey! Bamsı Bey!
-His wounds are severe. Quick!
-Alps! Prepare a sledge!
-Wait, my children.
Your Bamsı Bey is migrating
for the last time.
I beg you, Bamsı Bey. Don't speak
like that. You will be alright.
Don't worry, my daughter.
Don't worry.
Now...
The Mongol took one more life but...
they gave two valiant alps...
such as Cerkutay and Göktuğ.
Bamsı Bey...
Bamsı Bey!
Bamsı Bey! Bamsı Bey!
Bamsı Bey! What happened?
Bamsı Bey! Tell me!
What happened?
My lion, the valiant of Ertuğrul Bey!
My Osman.
Did you see?
I was sad that I wouldn't die a martyr.
-Bamsı Bey!
Bamsı Bey!
-Fate...
-No! No!
-No! You'll see many migrations.
You'll see many campaigns!
Don't!
-Don't!
-Son...
don't you see that it's my time?
Now I'll see my children.
May you see many migrations.
Bamsı Bey, don't leave us without
a father!
Bamsı Bey!
-Boran.
-My bey.
Aygül.
-Göktuğ...
-My bey!
Turan Alp! Turan Alp...
give me my swords.
Cerkutay...
now, these are yours.
I love you, my children.
-Osman.
-Tell me. Tell me, Bamsı Bey.
Now, my children are yours to protect.
Now, I know...
you'll take my revenge.
But...
firstly think for your tribe.
Bamsı Bey! Bamsı Bey!
Osman...
I have never...
doubted the state you will form.
But the state is forever.
The state is eternal.
Think about this.
-Bamsı Bey!
-Oh, Ertuğrul Bey?
Abdurrahman Ghazi!
Hamza! Hamza!
My lion...
It's time for testimony...
it's time for testimony.
I bear witness that there
is no god but Allah...
and I bear witness that Muhammad is...
the servant and Messenger...
of Allah.
Bamsı Bey.
Bamsı Bey...
A gift from my father...
a gift from my father.
The valiant alp who came from our
ancestral lands.
How happy I'm for you!
How happy I'm for that...
he who is as beautiful as his name...
our prophet Hz.Muhammed Mustafa,
may he rest in peace...
the bey you missed so much,
Ertuğrul Ghazi...
Abdurrahman Ghazi,
your martyr son...
and your beloved wife will greet you!
Bamsı Bey...
Now, age has ended.
That's the oath of Osman Bey,
son of Ertuğrul Ghazi!
A new age will start!
For the glory of our martyrs!
It will grow with vengeance!
These holy lands that you conquered...
Bamsı Bey!
Rest in peace.